CONTACT ME AT

JULIUS JASON JUNIO

Web Developer

Mobile: 438-998-1167 Address: Montreal, QC Email: jjjunio@gmail.com <u>Linkedin: Julius Jason Junio</u> <u>Github: jjjunio</u> <u>Behance: jjjunio</u>

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a full-stack web developer with 10 years of experience in the Healthcare industry with background in clinical, hospital, and academic settings. I am currently following my passion in design and coding to become a full stack web developer.

SKILLS

DATABASES

mvSQL

PostgreSQL

LANGUAGES

Javascript

Ruby

HTML

CSS

LIBRARIES AND FRAMEWORKS

Express

Rails

jQuery

React

Bootstrap

React Bootstrap

Mocha

Chai

Jest

Storybook

SASS

PLATFORMS

Git & Github

Node

DESIGN

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Lightroom

Marvel

PROJECTS

Foodbox

A web app connecting enabling home cooks to offer delicious home cooked meals for lunch to busy office workers.

Frameworks: React, Express, PostgreSQL, SASS

<u>Jungle</u>

Ruby on Rails e-commerce app tested with RSpec

Frameworks: Rails, Ruby, RSpec

Scheduler

A web app for scheduling appointments with interviewers for LHL

Frameworks: React, Jest, Storybook

Amazon Clone

Amazon clone made with React, Express, and Firebase

Frameworks: React, Express, Firebase

Netflix Clone

Netflix UI clone made with React and Firebase

Frameworks: React, Firebase

CAREER HISTORY

Occupational Health Nurse / Disability Case Manager

The Ottawa Hospital - General Campus April 2019 to April 2020

- Worked with department managers to improve short term, long term disability, and return to work timelines by closely managing injured/sick healthcare workers.
- Encouraged management to adopt online disability management tools to improve disability timelines and return to work outcomes.

Occupational Health Nurse / Disability Case Coordinator

University Health Network - Toronto Western Hospital April 2017 to August 2018

- Managed the non-complex return to work process, advising management and union on appropriate job placement for Toronto Western Hospital, including Altum Health all over Ontario.
- Coordinated with other Occupational Health Nurses and Disability case manager to improve departmental workflow by creating standard work for all departmental processes to improve turnover times and clinical services.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Lighthouse Labs, Montreal, QC

Web Development Diploma | April 2020 - July 2020

University of Victoria, Victoria, B.C.

Environmental and Occupational Health Certificate | June 2016 - June 2017

University of Makati, Philippines

B.Sc. Nursing | November 2006 - April 2009

University of the Philippines, Philippines

BSc Biology major in Genetics | June 2001 - April 2005